tablethotels.com 2018-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Tablet Hotels

Since the year 2000, the Tablet team has been committed to protecting the privacy and data of all of our clients and users around the world. Here at Tablet, we've never sold and will never sell your personal data to third parties. We also want to be transparent about the data that we collect, how we use it and your rights to control that information. This is why we have made some updates to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, which take effect on May 25, 2018.

We made these updates to reflect the high standards established by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a set of laws passed in the European Union. We embrace these changes and because we believe all Tablet clients and users should have the right to these protections, we are implementing these updates globally.

The GDPR applies to any information that directly or indirectly could identify you as an individual. This includes information, such as names, addresses, phone numbers, as well as IP addresses, cookie identifiers, device information, billing information, geo-location information, social media information, your preferences, etc.

As a registered client of Tablet Hotels, you can always see the information that you've shared with us in "Your Account".

We hope you'll find that these updates improve your customer experience and reinforce our commitment to your data privacy and security. If you have any questions or comments, send us a message at privacy@tablethotels.com. View our Terms of Use.

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy tells you about Tablet's policies and practices for the collection, use and disclosure of information we collect about you through our sites and services, including the website www.tablethotels.com and our mobile applications.

By using our sites and services, you accept and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## 1\. Definitions

Capitalized terms not otherwise defined below will have the following meanings:

  * _"Aggregated Information"_ means information recorded in any form about more than one individual, where the identity of the individual is not known and cannot be inferred from the information.
  * _"Guest"_ means an individual who searches Products or Services or makes Reservations on our Site without being a Member.
  * _"Member"_ means an individual who has registered on the www.tablethotels.com site.
  * _"Member ID"_ means the e-mail address Members use to log into our Site.
  * _"Personal Information"_ means any information, recorded in any form, about an identified individual, or an individual whose identity may be reasonably inferred from the information. This includes, for example, name, e-mail and mailing address, telephone number, billing and account information and other information incidental to providing Products or Services (including information about individuals traveling with an individual who makes Reservations on our Site).
  * _"Products or Services"_ means the hotel reservation and other items or services available from our Site.
  * _"Reservations"_ means executed orders to book a hotel through the Site.
  * _"Session Data"_ means usage information, such as the type of Internet browser and operating system an individual uses, the domain name of the site from which the individual came, the date, time and duration of the individual's visit, the number of visits, the pages viewed and the number of cookies accumulated.
  * _"Site"_ means www.tablethotels.com and its respective sub sites, content, Products and Services available therein.
  * _"Tablet," "we," "our,"_ or _"us"_ means Tablet Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates.

## 2\. Collection of Information

You can browse parts of our sites without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. Once you give us your Personal Information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with Personal Information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States. We may collect and store the following Personal Information:

  * name, employer's name, telephone numbers, email address, physical contact information, login, password, and financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers; 
  * transactional information based on your activities on the Site; 
  * correspondence through our Sites and correspondence sent to us; 
  * other information from your interaction with our Site, Services, content (including, without limitation content provided by third parties), and advertising; 
  * additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself; 
  * information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data; and 
  * other supplemental information from third parties.

We may obtain information from or about you in other ways. For example, we may verify user information with a service provider or combine your information with information we collect from other companies. Also, you may send us correspondence, testimonials, photos, writings, customer satisfaction surveys or customer service communications.

We may also offer you the chance to win a variety of travel or hotel-related prizes by sponsoring contests, promotions, raffles or sweepstakes. If you choose to participate in such a promotion, we will collect Personal Information from you to facilitate such contest. Where such contest is hosted or administered by a third-party, your participation may be subject to additional terms and conditions, including an additional privacy policy.

## 3\. Use of the Information We Collect

## 3.1. Personal Information

We don't sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our Products and Services, content and advertising.

Our primary purpose in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your Personal Information:

  * to provide the Products, Services and customer support you request;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * to record your preferences, make Reservations and communicate with you about your Reservations;
  * to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities such as negligence, breach of contract or fraud, and enforce our Terms and Conditions and other policies;
  * to audit compliance with our policies and contractual obligations;
  * to customize, measure and improve our Site, Services, Products, related content and advertising;
  * to tell you about our Products and Services, targeted marketing, updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;
  * as permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements or provisions; and
  * for any other purpose to which you affirmatively consent.

We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, Member ID, password, national identification numbers or related Personal Information in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

## 3.2. Aggregated Information

We may use Aggregated Information to describe our user base to current or potential partners, investors and advertisers; after a survey, to understand and respond to market needs and preferences; or to make recommendations to other users of our Site. For example, if users of our Site who have traveled to a particular destination told us that they had positive experiences at a hotel in that destination, we might recommend that hotel.

## 4\. How We Share Your Information

We may also share your Personal Information from time to time as follows:

  * to hotels and other third-party service providers with which you make arrangements through our Site;
  * to organizations that perform services for or on behalf of Tablet, such as couriers or shippers, credit card processors, marketing or research providers, data processors. NOTE: We will share with these companies only that Personal Information which they need to work on our behalf. Some of these service providers may be located in countries outside the US and outside the European Economic Area ("EEA").Your Personal Information will be provided to these organizations only if they agree to use such information solely for the purpose of providing services to Tablet, and under the instructions of Tablet, and with respect to that information, to act in a manner consistent with the relevant principles articulated in this Privacy Policy. By submitting your personal data, you agree to the transfer, storing and processing of your data outside the US and outside the EEA;
  * to third-parties with whom we are collaborating to offer you additional Products or Services such as sweepstakes, raffles and promotions. We will share Personal Information that is necessary for these other companies to provide the Products or Services that you have requested;
  * to protect our Site and our rights under our Terms and Conditions; to protect ourselves against liability or prevent fraudulent activity; or where it is necessary to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit any damages that we may sustain;
  * where the information is public; or
  * to regulatory agencies.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the Site free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your Personal Information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. In such circumstances, we will attempt to contact you, where permitted by law, before first making such disclosure.

## 5\. Storage, Retention and Protection of Personal Information

## 5.1. Storage and Retention

If you are a Member, we store your Personal Information in Your Account. You can access Your Account from the home page of our Site, after logging onto our Site. Your Account contains your name, e-mail address, e-mail and password settings, and related travel information. It may also contain other information so that you do not need to re-enter it each time you make a Reservation. It may also contain details about your participation in loyalty or awards programs and applicable membership numbers and other travel preferences. We also keep in Your Account all other information that you have elected to provide us, such as gender, activities and lifestyle preferences and favorite hotels or destinations. 

You can access or modify your account in Your Account. 

You can close your account by emailing [customerservice@tablethotels.com](mailto:customerservice@tablethotels.com).

We will retain in your Your Account, the Personal Information of individuals for whom you have made reservations on your behalf. You can access or modify these third parties' Personal Information at any time.

We will retain your Personal Information in our databases in accordance with our Records Management Policy and applicable laws. This period may extend beyond the end of your relationship with us, but it will be only as long as it is necessary for us to have sufficient information to respond to any issues that may arise later. We may also need to retain certain information to prevent fraudulent activity; protect ourselves against liability, permit us to pursue available remedies or limit any damages that we may sustain; or if we believe in good faith that a law, regulation, rule or guideline requires it.

Your Personal Information will be stored in secured locations and on servers controlled by Tablet, located either at our offices or at the offices of our service providers as described in "Protection of Information" below.

## 5.2. Protection of Personal Information

Tablet employs physical, administrative and technical safeguards to help protect the confidentiality and integrity of Personal Information and to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of Personal Information. When Personal Information is sent to our service providers, we require in our contracts with them that they protect all Personal Information in a manner consistent with the principles articulated in this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to contact Tablet through our Site, you should be aware that any information transmitted electronically via the World Wide Web might not be secure. Tablet assumes no liability for the loss of any information that you transmit to us via the World Wide Web. However, if you provide your credit card information on our Site's credit card forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

In communicating with you, we may send e-mail as unencrypted plain text because we are aware that most Members and Guests cannot readily process encrypted e-mail. This is done for your convenience, but with the security concern that, if misrouted or intercepted, it could be read more easily than encrypted e-mail.

## 5.3. Account Protection

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your Tablet password to anyone. If you do share your password or your Personal Information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your Personal Information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Tablet and change your password.

## 6\. How to access or modify your Account

You can access your Personal Information in Your Account. You can change at any time your preferences for receiving or not receiving our e-mails and e-newsletters.

If you wish to modify your Personal Information or close your account, you can do so by contacting us as indicated in Contact Information. We will respond to such requests to information access within thirty (30) days following receipt at the e-mail or mailing address stated above. If we receive your request at a different e-mail or mailing address, we will respond within a reasonable period of time.

We do retain Personal Information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

We may communicate with you at various times, with administrative emails or phone calls, about transactions and service announcements, customer service responses, and promotional emails like special offers, newsletters and updates. You can choose to stop receiving promotional emails at any time by simply using an email's unsubscribe function. You may not opt out of receiving administrative messages or customer service responses.

If you request that we close your account, we will promptly do so, to the extent possible. Once your account is closed, however, you will not be able to use many of the Services available on our Site to Members, unless you re-register.

Please remember that we may not be able to honor your request if we are legally obligated to retain information, or for other reasons described in "Storage, Retention and Protection of Personal Information" above.

## 7\. Privacy

## 7.1. Cookies Generally

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain of our pages to help analyze our web page flow; customize our services, content and advertising; measure promotional effectiveness; and promote trust and safety. When you first use our sites and services, Tablet may send a cookie to your computer that identifies you as a unique user. We may use session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to store your preferences, identify you and maintain your signed-in status, and provide you with a more personal and interactive experience. You can set your browser to refuse cookies or delete persistent cookies by following your browser's help instructions. If you choose to disable cookies, some of our services may not work properly and you may not be able to buy and sell items on Tablet.

We work with companies who may use cookies and web beacons to collect anonymous information that helps us measure and improve our content and advertising effectiveness. We may share some anonymous, aggregated demographic information (like zip codes) with some of our partners, but we do not share any personally identifiable information. You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the sites that we do not control.

## 7.2. Third Party Advertisers

We work with third parties to serve ads on our Site and to serve ads on sites owned or operated by other companies. Our ad servers, and those of our partners, use cookies and pixel tags in order to anonymously identify your browser. Some third-party ad companies, such as ad networks, may combine anonymous information obtained in connection with activity on our Site with information obtained from other sources and/or sites. We do not use or share any Personal Information with any of our ad server partners, media partners or ad networks without your authorization. 

We use anonymous Session Data, such as the destination of your search, in order to advertise to you on our Site and on other sites. We do not sell your Session Data to any other party in connection with our ad programs but we may use it in order to run ads on behalf of others, such as travel suppliers. If you wish to opt-out of this kind of advertising, you can click on the following link http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. None of our ad programs include any of your Personal Information. By opting out, you may still receive ads from Tablet or ads from other parties that are broadly targeted (not on the basis of your Session Data).

## 7.3. Opting-Out

As part of the registration process we give you the ability to receive via e-mail information about Products and Services, updates to our Site and customized advertisements and promotions that are targeted to your specific interests. We send this information directly ourselves or via third party service providers.

If you do not opt-out from receiving these communications about our Site, we will send them to you.

At any time you may change which of the communications you wish to receive or not, by changing your preferences under Your Account.

In addition, in our e-mails and other communications we will include instructions on how to unsubscribe and inform us of preferences if you decide you do not want to receive any future marketing or promotional e-mails from us.

## 7.4. Monitoring

Tablet may from time to time monitor and review any information transmitted or received through our Site, or through telephone or e-mail communications, for quality assurance and other purposes. We reserve the right to censor, edit, remove or prohibit the transmission or receipt of any information that Tablet deems inappropriate or in violation of our Terms and Conditions. During monitoring the information may be examined, recorded or copied.

## 7.5. Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others on our sites or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Tablet does not control the privacy policies of third-parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your Personal Information to others.

## 8\. General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the site. In addition, we will notify you of material changes with an alert on the Tablet site or a communication to you via email (at the e-mail address specified in your account) prior to the change becoming effective. If any proposed change is unacceptable to you, you may request that we close your account.

## 9\. U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks

Tablet complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union and Switzerland. Tablet adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. Information regarding the US-EU Safe Harbor and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks can be found at: [http://export.gov/safeharbor](https://export.gov/safeharbor). 

For European Union and Swiss Residents, if you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers located in the United States. Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of your information should be directed to Tablet by e-mailing us at [customerservice@tablethotels.com](mailto:customerservice@tablethotels.com). We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. European Union and Swiss Residents, if your complaints cannot be resolved, we have agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the American Arbitration Association pursuant to the US-EU Safe Harbor and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Principles.

## 10\. Contact Information

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at [feedback@tablethotels.com](mailto:feedback@tablethotels.com) or the following address:

Tablet Inc.  
6 West 18th Street  
New York, NY 10011 USA  
Tablet Inc. is a Delaware, USA Corporation
